https://www.chuckecheese.com/company/terms-and-privacy#CookiePolicy

Health & Safety
Re-Opening For Games, Birthdays & FUN!
Find Open Locations Now
Terms & PrivacyPRIVACYEffective Date: September 3, 2020CEC Entertainment Concepts, L.P. its parent company and its affiliates (collectively referred to herein as “CEC Entertainment”) are very respectful of the privacy concerns of the visitors to its site on the
Internet. This privacy policy applies to the following websites operated by CEC Entertainment: www.chuckecheese.com, franchise.chuckecheese.com, and www.pasquallyspizza.com (the “Websites”). This privacy policy describes how CEC Entertainment collects and uses the personal information you provide on the Websites. It also
describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACYCEC Entertainment makes a special effort to encourage children to consult with their parents before furnishing data. However, CEC Entertainment believes that parents should supervise their children’s online activities
and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their
name, address and other personal information without parental permission.We do not seek to acquire information specifically from children under the age of 13 on the Chuck E. Cheese website or its mobile applications.If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:CEC EntertainmentAttn.: Marketing Department1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063Phone number: 972-258-8507Email address: guestrelations@cecentertainment.comIf you have an unresolved privacy or data concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.Information Collection and UseWe collect the following personal information from you:Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone numberBilling Information such as credit card number, and billing addressWe also collect the following information from you:Birthdate, ages of children, shipping information, or other information that visitors voluntarily provideDemographic information such as zip code to help provide you with servicesWe use this information to:Complete party or event reservationsSend you an order confirmationSend Third Party’s email confirmation about party’s Send you a newsletterSend you marketing communicationSend you requested product or service informationSend product updates or warranty informationRespond to customer service requestsAdminister contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you wonRespond to your questions and concernsImprove our website and marketing effortsConduct research and analysisGeo-Location DataWe do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our Mobile Applications or Services. However, our website does ask you for, access or
track any location based information so that we may enhance your experience on our website (e.g., locating a nearby Chuck E. Cheese or identifying special offers that may be of interest to you, or personalizing your
interactions with us). For most mobile devices, you are able to withdraw your permission for us to acquire this information on your location through the device settings. If you have questions about how to disable your
mobile device's location services, we recommend you contact your mobile device service provider or the device manufacturer. If you would like us to delete location information we have collected, please contact us at
the email or postal address listed below. Please note that the website may not function properly following deletion, and that we may be required by law to retain certain information.
Device InformationWhen you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and the operating system version so that we may provide you with the correct version of our application(s).Information SharingWe will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.Service ProvidersWe may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, processing your payment, or offering customer services. These companies are
authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.Legal DisclaimerWe may also disclose your personal information:In certain situations, CEC Entertainment may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements as required
by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud,
or respond to a government request.If CEC Entertainment is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your
personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.Name of third-party partnerWhat info is shared with or collected by this partner?Partner’s purposeLink to partner’s privacy policyGoogle Inc. (YouTube)Analytics, visitor traffic statsYouTube, website tools, ad platform, analyticshttp://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Microsoft (Atlas Solutions)User Internet usage/behavior (no PII)Ad network, advertisinghttp://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/default.mspxTwitter Inc.Page linksSocial sharinghttps://twitter.com/privacyInstagramPage links, likesSocial sharinghttps://help.instagram.com/155833707900388PinterestPage links, pinsSocial sharinghttps://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policyFacebookPage links, likesSocial sharinghttps://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/AppnexusUser Internet usage/behavior (no PII)Ad networkhttp://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policyMediaplex / ConversantUser Internet usage/behavior (no PII)Ad platformhttp://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacyDouble ClickUser Internet usage/behavior (no PII)Ad platformhttp://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Google AdsenseUser Internet usage/behavior (no PII)Ad networkhttp://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/The chart lists the names of some of our third party partners and support provider entities, which may provide administrative services to our Websites. These entities may change from time to time and we will update this
list as soon as practicable following any changes.If you have any inquiries regarding our partner’s privacy practices or how they use your child’s personal information, please contact us directly at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com.
User Access and Choice Upon your request CEC Entertainment will confirm for you whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update,
or request deletion of personally identifiable information collected by contacting us by emailing our Customer Support at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact
information listed below. To safeguard your information, we will also take steps to verify your identity before granting access or correction. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Although we do
not seek to collect information from children, parents may, after providing proper parental identification, request to review, update, or delete their own child's information that may have been submitted and refuse
to allow CEC Entertainment to collect further information about their child by emailing our Customer Support at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information
listed below. Parents who provide information of their under 13 child can consent to collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes,
and enforce our agreements.Opt-out PreferencesOut of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. We do send transactional emails when processing your orders and
responding to your feedback/questions. You may not opt out of these emails as they are not promotional in nature.Reservation DepositsWe require a non-refundable $50 deposit to secure your reservation.  The deposit will be applied towards your party total on the day of the party.  Your reservation may be cancelled and/or rescheduled at any time.
If you need to cancel, your reservation the non-refundable deposit can be used towards a new reservation within one (1) year of the reserved date of the party that was cancelled.  The billing descriptor you
will see on your credit/bank statement will be portrayed as “CHUCK E CHEESE DEPOSIT”Agreement to Contact UsWe are eager to offer the best customer experience possible. Please contact our Guest Relations team prior to contacting your credit card issuer to allow us to resolve any issues or concerns with our services.  You can reach us by email at ceconline@cecentertainment.com
or toll-free at 833-268-2201.  We are available from (Monday-Friday 8am-5pm (CT)). Expect a 72-hour response time for email inquiries.SurveysWe may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests
is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic
information (such as ZIP code).We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send
participants an email newsletter, or contact if there are issues. We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally
identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.Tracking TechnologiesTechnologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts are used by us and our tracking utility company who provides online customer support. These technologies are used in improving the user experience for completing
forms for the reservation process, tracking behaviors so that we can provide relevant messaging and improve the overall experience, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information
about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.Analytics / Log FilesAs is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit
pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the
site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This data is used to track Internet usage and behavior so that we can retarget you with relevant messaging and to improve the user experience.Local Storage (HTML5)Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use Local Storage also known as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various
browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.Behavioral Advertising/RetargetingWe partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities
on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you
may opt out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.Data SupplementationWe may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.
Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include:Address information about you from third party sources, such as the U.S. Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.Purchased marketing data about our customers from third parties that is combined with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.Mobile AnalyticsWe use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur
within the application, aggregated usage, performance data and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit
within the mobile application, as we do not collect any personal information through the application.SecurityThe security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer
technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of
electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com.Additional Information Links to Third-Party SitesOur site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of CEC Entertainment. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies.
We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.To provide certain animated features on our site, we use Macromedia Shockwave, Macromedia Flash, Adobe Acrobat, and Apple's QuickTime ActiveX
plugins, which will automatically prompt you for download if your browser does not contain the latest version. Apple and Adobe use the information collected through these applications according to their own privacy
and security policies, which can be further evaluated at: http://www.apple.com/quicktime and http://www.adobe.comTestimonialsFrom time to time, we display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or
delete your testimonial, you can contact us at guestrelations@cecentertainment.com.Social Media WidgetsOur website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and widgets, such as the “Share this” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect
your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our
site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTSCalifornia Civil Code Section 1798.83 allows our California customers to request certain information regarding our disclosures in the prior calendar year, if any, of personally identifiable information to third parties
for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at either
guestrelations@cecentertainment.com or CEC Entertainment,1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063, Attn: Marketing Department, and include your name
and the address to which you would like us to respond. We will attempt to provide you with the requested information within thirty (30) days of receipt.Changes To This PolicyWe may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices at any time. Notice will be given when the privacy policy is changed. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent
to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy
practices.
Contact UsCEC EntertainmentAttn.: Marketing Department1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063Phone number: 972-258-8507Email address: guestrelations@cecentertainment.comTERMS OF USEPlease read these Terms Of Use carefully before using this site. By using this site, you are agreeing to these Terms Of Use. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms Of Use, do not use this site. CEC Entertainment
Concepts, L.P. (CEC Entertainment) reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms Of Use at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.Regardless of changes in these Terms Of Use, personally identifiable information will never be used in ways materially different than stated in these Terms of Use without first providing you a meaningful opportunity to
opt out or prevent that use.TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS AND RESTRICTIONSThe Websites are controlled and operated by CEC Entertainment, 1707 Market Place Blvd, Suite 200, Irving, TX 75063. The phone number is 972-258-8507. Email address guestrelations@cecentertainment.com. All materials on this
site, including, but not limited to images, illustrations, audio clips, and video clips, are protected by copyrights that are owned and controlled by CEC Entertainment or by other parties that have licensed their material
to CEC Entertainment. (“Copyrights”). Material from the websites as well as any other website owned, operated, licensed or controlled by CEC Entertainment (“CEC
Entertainment websites”) may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation
of the copyrights and other proprietary rights. For purposes of this Terms of Use Agreement, the use of any such material on any other website or networked computer environment is prohibited.WARRANTIES DISCLAIMERMaterials on the Chuck E. Cheese website are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind either express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, CEC Entertainment disclaims
all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. CEC Entertainment does not warrant that the functions contained in the materials
will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, nor the server that makes them available are free of viruses or other harmful components. CEC Entertainment does not warrant or make any representations
regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials in CEC Entertainment websites in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You (and not CEC Entertainment) assume the entire cost of
all necessary servicing, repair or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you. Material on the Chuck E. Cheese website is provided solely
for entertainment and promotional purposes. Any notes, message/billboard postings, ideas, suggestions, concepts or other material submitted will become the property of CEC Entertainment throughout the universe and CEC
Entertainment, subject only to the privacy portions of this statement controlling the use of personally identifiable information, shall be entitled to use the material for any type of use forever including in any media
whether now known or hereafter devised. You agree to indemnify CEC Entertainment and its officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors and affiliates from and against any and all third-party claims, demands,
liabilities, costs, or expenses, including reasonable attorney’s fees, resulting from your breach of any of the foregoing agreements, representations, and warranties.EMAILS AND POSTINGS RECEIVEDDo not post any threatening or libelous emails or material on this site that would be considered a violation of any law. CEC Entertainment will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting
or directing CEC Entertainment to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such emails or materials.JURISDICTIONAL ISSUESUnless otherwise specified, the materials in Chuck E. Cheese website are presented solely for the purpose of entertainment and promotion. This site is controlled and operated by CEC Entertainment from its offices within
the State of Texas, United States of America. CEC Entertainment makes no representation that materials in Chuck E. Cheese website are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this
site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. This agreement shall be governed by, construed and enforced
in accordance with the laws of the State of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party or CEC Entertainment bring to enforce this
agreement or, in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Dallas, Texas and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If
any provision of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any
remaining provisions. This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by CEC Entertainment. Except for disputes regarding
the collection and use of personally identifiable information, which may be processed through the TRUSTe Privacy Dispute Resolution Service, this agreement shall otherwise be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance
with the laws of the State of Texas, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such State. Any action you, any third party or CEC Entertainment bring to enforce this agreement or,
in connection with, any matters related to this site shall be brought only in either the state or Federal Courts located in Dallas, Texas and you expressly consent to the jurisdiction of said courts. If any provision
of this agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
This is the entire agreement between the parties relating to the matters contained herein and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by CEC Entertainment.JOB APPLICANT SMSWhen you provide your telephone number as part of your application for employment with CEC Entertainment you agree to receive text/SMS messages concerning future job opportunities subject to the terms below.  IMPORTANT NOTE: By opting in to receive text/SMS messages you are also opting in to receive autodialed ads and other marketing messages/calls. By opting in you agree that CEC Entertainment may send you up to
six (6) text/SMS  autodialed ads and other marketing messages. Residents of Canada are not eligible to receive Text/SMS messages and will not be provided the ability to opt-in.By providing us your mobile
telephone number and opting-in to such calls and text/SMS messages, you represent that you are the owner of the mobile telephone associated with that mobile telephone number and that you are responsible for controlling
access to that mobile telephone. You agree to notify CEC Entertainment of any change to your mobile telephone number. If you opt-in to receive autodialed and prerecorded calls or text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment
and then change your mobile telephone number, you agree that CEC Entertainment may continue to send text/SMS messages, or autodialed and prerecorded calls to you at the new mobile telephone number unless you opt-out
as described below. Depending on the terms of your service agreement with your mobile telecommunications service provider message and data rates may apply to the text/SMS messages and autodialed and prerecorded call
that CEC Entertainment send to your mobile telephone number. Supported carriers for CEC Entertainment text/SMS messages are: AT&T, Verizon, T-Mobile, and Metro PCS (at a minimum.) Please note, T-Mobile is not liable
for delayed or undelivered messages.Your consent is not a condition of making any employment decisions. Message and data rates may apply. For help, text HELP to 972-449-7899.HOW TO OPT-OUT OF AND STOP
TEXT/SMS MESSAGES:If you wish to opt-out of and stop receiving text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment, reply to our text/SMS message with “STOP” or by sending “STOP” to  972-449-7899.If you opt-in to receive text/SMS messages from CEC Entertainment and later opt-out of receiving text/SMS messages from us, you agree that CEC Entertainment may send a text/SMS message to your mobile telephone
number to confirm that you have opted-out of receiving text/SMS messages from us.CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 2018 (“CCPA”)We adopt this notice to comply with the CCPA (effective 2020) and other California privacy laws.  Any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this notice.  The CCPA provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. In accordance with the CCPA, California consumers may exercise under certain conditions the following four (4) categories of privacy rights with respect to their personal information. Please note: you will not be discriminated against in any way by virtue of your exercises of the rights listed below, which means we will not deny goods or services to you, provide different rates for those goods or services, or provide a different level or quality for those goods or services.Access to Specific Information and Data Portability RightsYou have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:The categories of personal information we collected about you.The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing: sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.Deletion Request RightsYou have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you;Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities;Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law;Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.);Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent;Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us;Comply with a legal obligation; orMake other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion RightsTo exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either:Calling us at 972-258-8507Visiting [www.chuckecheese.com or www.peterpiperpizza.com]Emailing guestrelations@cecentertainment.comOnly you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative; andDescribe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.  Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.  We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.Response Timing and FormatWe endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt.  If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.  If you have an account with us, we will deliver our written response to that account.  If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option.  Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request's receipt.  The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.  For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.FeeWe do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.  If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Kids Privacy Assured by PRIVO: COPPA Safe Harbor CertificationCEC Entertainment, Inc is a member of the PRIVO Kids Privacy Assured COPPA Safe Harbor Certification Program (“the Program”). The Program certification applies to the digital properties listed on the validation page that is viewable by clicking on the PRIVO Seal. PRIVO is an independent, third-party organization committed to safeguarding children's personal information collected online. The PRIVO COPPA certification Seal posted on this page indicates CEC Entertainment, Inc has established COPPA compliant privacy practices and has agreed to submit to PRIVO’s oversight and consumer dispute resolution process. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at 1-888-778-7193 or GuestRelations@cecentertainment.com. If you have further concerns after you have contacted us, you can contact PRIVO directly at privacy@privo.com.
Chuck E. Cheese uses cookies.
Find out how by clicking
here.
By continuing to use our site you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with our
Terms and Privacy Policy footer.
ACCEPT
Find A Location
Address
%%preferredStore.address%% %%preferredStore.address_extended%%
%%preferredStore.locality%%, %%preferredStore.region%% %%preferredStore.postcode%%
© 2020 CEC Entertainment, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
